mitre.org 2017-03-12

# Privacy Policy | The MITRE Corporation

> MITRE respects the privacy of its website users. 

MITRE respects the privacy of its website users. This privacy policy explains the types of information collected from site visitors, and how MITRE uses that information. The use of the MITRE website constitutes acceptance of this policy.

**Information Collected from Web Traffic Reporting Tools**

When users visit the MITRE website, the website server logs basic information about each visit. We process this information monthly via an automated software tool to identify any site performance issues, popular sections and content, and other important site characteristics. This information does not identify you personally. This information is used only as a source of anonymous statistical information. We may store such information ourselves, or it may be included in databases owned and maintained by our service providers.

MITRE employs cookies for collecting portions of this information. "Cookies" are data that may be sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. Most web browsers can be configured not to accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you. If you wish not to have cookies set during your visit to the MITRE website, you can disable them in your web browser. The raw log data is retained for a minimum of 90 days.

MITRE also uses a free third party software service called Google Analytics® to capture and analyze website usage information. This service supplies us with additional non-personally identifiable information about MITRE's website users to help us create content that our users may find useful. Users that wish to have their non-personally identifiable information not collected by means of their visit to the MITRE website have the option to opt-out of the Google Analytics tracking service via this link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

**Information Collected from E-mail and Web Forms**

Users may contact MITRE by postal mail, telephone, or electronically, using information found on the Contact Us page. MITRE may share the information that you provide to us via e-mail within the corporation to respond to your queries, but we do not provide information to anyone outside of the corporation unless required by law to do so. We will never share your information with a third party for any commercial purpose.

**Information Collected from Employment Applications**

Users may apply for employment at MITRE from within the Employment section of our website, using the systems of one of our vendors. The information you supply is collected by our vendor and accessed by our vendor and MITRE during the application process. For additional information about our vendor's Privacy Policy, please see their [website](http://www.kenexa.com/privacy-policy).

**Information Collected from Third Party Software**

When users visit the MITRE website, users may link to third party software when they link to another party's website. MITRE does not collect any information that may be collected by that third party; however, information you supply to that third party software may be collected and/or used by that party. For information about that third party's Privacy Policy, please see their respective website.

**Information Collected from Third Party Media Sites**

MITRE currently uses Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, and YouTube as third party media sites. MITRE does not collect any information that may be collected by that third party; however, information you supply to that third party software may be collected by that party. For information about that third party's Privacy Policy, please see their respective website.

**Information Collected from Smartphone Applications**

MITRE does not collect any information that may be collected by a smartphone application; however, information you supply to that smartphone application may be collected by that party. For information about that third party's Privacy Policy, please see their respective website.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

The MITRE website may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, MITRE reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any information. Your continued use of the MITRE website after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.
